{
    "subject": "resource/Pat_Green",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Pat Green",
    "human_readable": "The name of Pat Green is Pat Green.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9763868451118469,
            "question": "What is the name of Pat Green?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9621531367301941,
            "question": "Is Pat Green known by another name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9338371753692627,
            "question": "What kind of person is Pat Green?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.878564178943634,
            "question": "Is there anything surprising about the name Pat Green?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6819059252738953,
            "question": "Can you tell me something about Pat Green?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6595832705497742,
            "question": "Does Pat Green have a different profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6192354559898376,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Pat Green?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6033356189727783,
            "question": "Where might we find more information about Pat Green?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5849458575248718,
            "question": "How would you describe Pat Green in a few words?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5516847968101501,
            "question": "What do you think is important to know about Pat Green?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Pat Green is Pat Green.",
            "html": "dbpedia_516_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Pat Green in a few words?",
            "html": "dbpedia_516_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might we find more information about Pat Green?",
            "html": "dbpedia_516_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about Pat Green?",
            "html": "dbpedia_516_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_516_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Pat Green, including his name, which matches the query \"The name of Pat Green is Pat Green.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}